[
    {
        "prompt": "Frances Travis has a job of",
        "answer": "guide"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Willie Person has a job of",
        "answer": "serviceman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dylan Fowler has a job of",
        "answer": "skipper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kameron Dejesus has a job of",
        "answer": "neat person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julissa Calhoun has a job of",
        "answer": "fbi agent"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gary Graves has a job of",
        "answer": "gunsmith"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rhys McKinney has a job of",
        "answer": "veterinarian"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gwendolyn Day has a job of",
        "answer": "deacon"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kayson McMahon has a job of",
        "answer": "country woman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Belen Humphrey has a job of",
        "answer": "relay racer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lilah Barrett has a job of",
        "answer": "gentleman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Angelo Ross has a job of",
        "answer": "tennis player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Peyton Simmons has a job of",
        "answer": "teenager"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harrison Doyle has a job of",
        "answer": "warder"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Annalise Wilkerson has a job of",
        "answer": "tue gentleman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Carmelo Burnett has a job of",
        "answer": "service man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emberly Person has a job of",
        "answer": "pessimist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Moses Ayala has a job of",
        "answer": "trader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Blair Bullock has a job of",
        "answer": "supermodel"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ben Davidson has a job of",
        "answer": "meter maid"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jayla O\u2019Connell has a job of",
        "answer": "drummer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jovanni Boyer has a job of",
        "answer": "carpenter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Chaya Hail has a job of",
        "answer": "technician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emmalyn Daniels has a job of",
        "answer": "lion tamer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kaliyah Berry has a job of",
        "answer": "dealer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adonis Lucas has a job of",
        "answer": "fit woman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Colter Barber has a job of",
        "answer": "car buyer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rex Bishop has a job of",
        "answer": "computer programmer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brooklynn Caldwell has a job of",
        "answer": "pastry chef"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rylan Hawkins has a job of",
        "answer": "council"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ariel Kirk has a job of",
        "answer": "good driver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alessandro Bennett has a job of",
        "answer": "karate master"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Josephine Valdez has a job of",
        "answer": "slacker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kyler Knapp has a job of",
        "answer": "pastor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Linda Lambert has a job of",
        "answer": "negative person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mario Contreras has a job of",
        "answer": "family court judge"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Daniela Erickson has a job of",
        "answer": "repairman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Johnny Vargas has a job of",
        "answer": "cabinet maker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tucker Farmer has a job of",
        "answer": "foreman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hezekiah Mueller has a job of",
        "answer": "poor typist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kye Haynes has a job of",
        "answer": "pizza delivery guy"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lexi Pham has a job of",
        "answer": "birdwatcher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Russell Coleman has a job of",
        "answer": "headhunter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julia Sherman has a job of",
        "answer": "designer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adan Wong has a job of",
        "answer": "merchandiser"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adelaide Hanna has a job of",
        "answer": "careful person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aydin Conrad has a job of",
        "answer": "bookkeeper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bexley Lucero has a job of",
        "answer": "language student"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Arabella Pitts has a job of",
        "answer": "star athlete"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Trey Harper has a job of",
        "answer": "tailor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ana Campbell has a job of",
        "answer": "master mariner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Christopher Cherry has a job of",
        "answer": "store clerk"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nyomi Martinez has a job of",
        "answer": "hypnotist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alexander Parks has a job of",
        "answer": "world traveler"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ainsley Branch has a job of",
        "answer": "great baseball player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Avery Cross has a job of",
        "answer": "circus clown"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Chaya Stark has a job of",
        "answer": "lumberjack"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kristopher Joseph has a job of",
        "answer": "performer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gracelynn Montoya has a job of",
        "answer": "window washer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Khloe Meza has a job of",
        "answer": "gallery visitor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Oaklynn Brock has a job of",
        "answer": "shortstop"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julio Raymond has a job of",
        "answer": "retailer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hadlee Frederick has a job of",
        "answer": "violinist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kase Tanner has a job of",
        "answer": "joker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harmoni Hogan has a job of",
        "answer": "city dweller"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sonny Burke has a job of",
        "answer": "great basketball player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Laylah McKay has a job of",
        "answer": "fair judge"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Joey Rosario has a job of",
        "answer": "baseball pitcher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Louisa Esparza has a job of",
        "answer": "seamstress"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Carl Campbell has a job of",
        "answer": "debater"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Addison Wong has a job of",
        "answer": "senior citizen"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Walter Salinas has a job of",
        "answer": "chairman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Royalty Quinn has a job of",
        "answer": "bird watcher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kaylee Fernandez has a job of",
        "answer": "stupid person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bentley Bradshaw has a job of",
        "answer": "horse trainer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Berkley Gaines has a job of",
        "answer": "peasant"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Annabelle Moran has a job of",
        "answer": "mathematician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tate Hicks has a job of",
        "answer": "fat man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alina Moore has a job of",
        "answer": "hero"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jocelyn Bentley has a job of",
        "answer": "mason"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Randy Mayo has a job of",
        "answer": "very lucky person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aarya Avalos has a job of",
        "answer": "manager"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Marcelo Tucker has a job of",
        "answer": "columnist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Esther Boone has a job of",
        "answer": "timekeeper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mauricio Berg has a job of",
        "answer": "coalminer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emmalyn Walters has a job of",
        "answer": "great dancer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Colson Murray has a job of",
        "answer": "foolhardy person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Faith Evans has a job of",
        "answer": "dietician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elias McCoy has a job of",
        "answer": "creative person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Easton Rojas has a job of",
        "answer": "defense attorney"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ronald Galvan has a job of",
        "answer": "meterologist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dallas Rush has a job of",
        "answer": "skier"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Monica Vaughan has a job of",
        "answer": "truck driver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Castiel Rocha has a job of",
        "answer": "restaurant patron"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emmie Richard has a job of",
        "answer": "courier"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ahmed Fitzgerald has a job of",
        "answer": "referee"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Marlee Montes has a job of",
        "answer": "bride"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Darren Mack has a job of",
        "answer": "rich man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nadia Chambers has a job of",
        "answer": "diver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Orion Stevens has a job of",
        "answer": "butcher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Katherine Randolph has a job of",
        "answer": "brewer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lilian Cooper has a job of",
        "answer": "builder"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jonathan Stokes has a job of",
        "answer": "wine grader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Miranda Cantu has a job of",
        "answer": "construction worker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Anakin Morris has a job of",
        "answer": "housekeeper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Genesis Wilson has a job of",
        "answer": "rockstars"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Daniel Nixon has a job of",
        "answer": "groom"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Deborah Burns has a job of",
        "answer": "swimmer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "August Bernal has a job of",
        "answer": "sneaky spy"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emmeline Long has a job of",
        "answer": "fast food clerk"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jace Beck has a job of",
        "answer": "published author"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gia Lowe has a job of",
        "answer": "camper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julius Hayes has a job of",
        "answer": "detective"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Iris Bush has a job of",
        "answer": "ticket agent"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alfredo McMillan has a job of",
        "answer": "middle school student"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Oakleigh Li has a job of",
        "answer": "peaceful person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jorge Gardner has a job of",
        "answer": "pianist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elisha Wong has a job of",
        "answer": "martial artist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adelaide Ross has a job of",
        "answer": "fishmonger"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wesley Moon has a job of",
        "answer": "governmental leader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Naya Arellano has a job of",
        "answer": "phone operator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kellan Foley has a job of",
        "answer": "receiver in football game"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zaylee Patterson has a job of",
        "answer": "guilty person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Amir Roach has a job of",
        "answer": "famous singer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lyanna Cantrell has a job of",
        "answer": "drunk people"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harris Walters has a job of",
        "answer": "mentor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Roberto Evans has a job of",
        "answer": "shop clerk"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Eliana Garrett has a job of",
        "answer": "polyamourous person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Malaya Horn has a job of",
        "answer": "tour guide"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Whitley Vargas has a job of",
        "answer": "censor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Madisyn Goodman has a job of",
        "answer": "skater"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Philip Curry has a job of",
        "answer": "horseman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kamryn Hayes has a job of",
        "answer": "golfer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Legend English has a job of",
        "answer": "moderaters"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kelly Aguirre has a job of",
        "answer": "janator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Andy Hale has a job of",
        "answer": "job seeker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brinley Bennett has a job of",
        "answer": "pretty girl"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Leonardo Conley has a job of",
        "answer": "professional dancer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Salem Ball has a job of",
        "answer": "hardy sailor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Makayla Esquivel has a job of",
        "answer": "packer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bridger Monroe has a job of",
        "answer": "farmhand"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Carly Reynolds has a job of",
        "answer": "secretary"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vincent Ball has a job of",
        "answer": "drunk driver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Abby Salas has a job of",
        "answer": "tenor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zaiden Bailey has a job of",
        "answer": "healthy person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kennedy Leblanc has a job of",
        "answer": "commuter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Braden Bradshaw has a job of",
        "answer": "supermarket employee"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Berkley Taylor has a job of",
        "answer": "hard worker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jackson Stein has a job of",
        "answer": "relay runner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Leilany Vasquez has a job of",
        "answer": "historian"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rowan Monroe has a job of",
        "answer": "repairer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Carly Murillo has a job of",
        "answer": "dictator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lance McKee has a job of",
        "answer": "terrible cook"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kori Phan has a job of",
        "answer": "nurse"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Maison Meyer has a job of",
        "answer": "gatekeeper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sara Caldwell has a job of",
        "answer": "tourist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rylan Ho has a job of",
        "answer": "good teacher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Calliope Lynn has a job of",
        "answer": "perceptive man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zechariah Henry has a job of",
        "answer": "patient person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Greyson Tucker has a job of",
        "answer": "fisherman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Esther Reed has a job of",
        "answer": "counter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Easton Bond has a job of",
        "answer": "developer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alena Stanley has a job of",
        "answer": "weightlifter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Manuel Dalton has a job of",
        "answer": "loyal person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lilian Abbott has a job of",
        "answer": "medical doctor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bridget Patel has a job of",
        "answer": "smart person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Parker Haynes has a job of",
        "answer": "band leader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lexi Blair has a job of",
        "answer": "lobbyist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Troy Ali has a job of",
        "answer": "top notch salesperson"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zelda Hamilton has a job of",
        "answer": "salesman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jason Krueger has a job of",
        "answer": "baby sitter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kamari Liu has a job of",
        "answer": "circus trainer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Pedro Boyer has a job of",
        "answer": "voodoo artist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Chaya Sexton has a job of",
        "answer": "hungry person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mylo Frank has a job of",
        "answer": "concierge"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dilan Rojas has a job of",
        "answer": "great salesman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "April Berry has a job of",
        "answer": "great singer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adonis Clay has a job of",
        "answer": "warrior"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rogelio Houston has a job of",
        "answer": "storekeeper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lylah Tang has a job of",
        "answer": "lonely person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emmalynn Reese has a job of",
        "answer": "craftsman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alijah Knox has a job of",
        "answer": "psychiatrist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lincoln Yoder has a job of",
        "answer": "good scientist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emerie Sharp has a job of",
        "answer": "rancher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Royce Haley has a job of",
        "answer": "landscaper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Addilynn Ramsey has a job of",
        "answer": "trumpet player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bodie Hardy has a job of",
        "answer": "fat person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jessica Day has a job of",
        "answer": "sunbather"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kayson Weeks has a job of",
        "answer": "skeptical person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Karsyn Bass has a job of",
        "answer": "champion"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zahra Valdez has a job of",
        "answer": "pornstar"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kyler Owen has a job of",
        "answer": "baseball player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mikayla Moyer has a job of",
        "answer": "poker player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ahmir Morales has a job of",
        "answer": "knight"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Skylar Gillespie has a job of",
        "answer": "scuba diver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Forest Gentry has a job of",
        "answer": "princess"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Amelie Carr has a job of",
        "answer": "machinist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kash Booker has a job of",
        "answer": "launderer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nataly Weiss has a job of",
        "answer": "counselor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Koa Salinas has a job of",
        "answer": "cyclist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kayson Benson has a job of",
        "answer": "ballplayer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tristan Maldonado has a job of",
        "answer": "clumsy person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elaina Corona has a job of",
        "answer": "chief"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Darian Rivera has a job of",
        "answer": "saxophone player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lillian Fletcher has a job of",
        "answer": "lighthousekeepers"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harleigh Jones has a job of",
        "answer": "military person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "William Bruce has a job of",
        "answer": "star football player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Marilyn Payne has a job of",
        "answer": "sharp negotiator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Edward Wilson has a job of",
        "answer": "mature person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Luna Griffin has a job of",
        "answer": "busy person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ayden Nichols has a job of",
        "answer": "storyteller"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aliyah Gaines has a job of",
        "answer": "runner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Talon Guevara has a job of",
        "answer": "merchant"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Teresa Castro has a job of",
        "answer": "researcher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jasper Leonard has a job of",
        "answer": "clerk"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Demi Pierce has a job of",
        "answer": "rich investor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Miracle Shannon has a job of",
        "answer": "servant"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nelson Gould has a job of",
        "answer": "good reporter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Damir Peralta has a job of",
        "answer": "gardener"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Malayah Clark has a job of",
        "answer": "rock roll star"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "John Houston has a job of",
        "answer": "weaponsman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lylah Barnes has a job of",
        "answer": "typist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sunny Hull has a job of",
        "answer": "single parent"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Salem Chapman has a job of",
        "answer": "persistent person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Pablo Horton has a job of",
        "answer": "volunteer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aitana Jarvis has a job of",
        "answer": "pregnant woman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Marlon Pace has a job of",
        "answer": "police man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Giana Le has a job of",
        "answer": "player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Damien Burns has a job of",
        "answer": "quitter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emerson Santiago has a job of",
        "answer": "maid"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Beckham Dalton has a job of",
        "answer": "meat cutter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lilian Gates has a job of",
        "answer": "mean guy"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ermias Blackburn has a job of",
        "answer": "hardworking homemaker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Frida Gregory has a job of",
        "answer": "qa engineer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Travis Barrett has a job of",
        "answer": "policman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Archie Holt has a job of",
        "answer": "shipper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adelynn Owens has a job of",
        "answer": "stewardess"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adriel Rosario has a job of",
        "answer": "cook"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Peter Esquivel has a job of",
        "answer": "saxaphone player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jaylee Ramirez has a job of",
        "answer": "naive person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "David Ray has a job of",
        "answer": "judge"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ruth Hartman has a job of",
        "answer": "wise leader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Baker Bender has a job of",
        "answer": "mediator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lilyana Potts has a job of",
        "answer": "mayor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alfred Gardner has a job of",
        "answer": "critical person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jordyn Gardner has a job of",
        "answer": "clever person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alan Murillo has a job of",
        "answer": "footballer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mikaela Ingram has a job of",
        "answer": "guard"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tripp Day has a job of",
        "answer": "shoe salesman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hayden Park has a job of",
        "answer": "puzzle solver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Daxton Yates has a job of",
        "answer": "dreamer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Charley Mahoney has a job of",
        "answer": "goalie"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kamryn Lawrence has a job of",
        "answer": "jury"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lauren Graham has a job of",
        "answer": "shop owner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Giovanni Burton has a job of",
        "answer": "director"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Miriam Robles has a job of",
        "answer": "fashion model"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Otto Harrison has a job of",
        "answer": "pompous person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jasmine Olsen has a job of",
        "answer": "winemaker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Skyler Hartman has a job of",
        "answer": "spendthrift"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Madelynn Mata has a job of",
        "answer": "geographer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ray Wilson has a job of",
        "answer": "greedy monopolist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Luna Krueger has a job of",
        "answer": "pilot"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jones Lu has a job of",
        "answer": "good rider"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emani Kent has a job of",
        "answer": "philanthropist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mekhi Hodge has a job of",
        "answer": "restaurant hostess"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Coraline Trejo has a job of",
        "answer": "critic"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wesson Norman has a job of",
        "answer": "musician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Salem Gomez has a job of",
        "answer": "football coach"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Natalie Strickland has a job of",
        "answer": "restaurant worker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Keegan Ali has a job of",
        "answer": "woodcutter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zelda Whitehead has a job of",
        "answer": "bowler"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zayd Aguirre has a job of",
        "answer": "percussionist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ariah Duarte has a job of",
        "answer": "landowner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Abdullah Clark has a job of",
        "answer": "gladiator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Chloe Schaefer has a job of",
        "answer": "policeman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ishaan Strickland has a job of",
        "answer": "government leader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nia O\u2019Neill has a job of",
        "answer": "filmmaker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Marcel Merritt has a job of",
        "answer": "fisher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lachlan Sherman has a job of",
        "answer": "story teller"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Addilyn Ball has a job of",
        "answer": "consumer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shane Sheppard has a job of",
        "answer": "good crew"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dane Lim has a job of",
        "answer": "batter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Giavanna Durham has a job of",
        "answer": "soprano"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kellen Fowler has a job of",
        "answer": "socialist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Shane Mora has a job of",
        "answer": "good technician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jemma Zamora has a job of",
        "answer": "cautious person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Quentin Davidson has a job of",
        "answer": "breeder"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jayla Sherman has a job of",
        "answer": "professional basketball player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adan Owen has a job of",
        "answer": "drunk person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mikayla Fernandez has a job of",
        "answer": "logical person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bentley Gibbs has a job of",
        "answer": "courageous person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Carter Brandt has a job of",
        "answer": "politician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Damir Moreno has a job of",
        "answer": "stargazer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mary Wilcox has a job of",
        "answer": "security guard"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gemma Simmons has a job of",
        "answer": "dairy producer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harrison Montoya has a job of",
        "answer": "soldier"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kamryn Archer has a job of",
        "answer": "voyager"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alora Sierra has a job of",
        "answer": "pitcher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dayton Baker has a job of",
        "answer": "soccer player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Malachi Jimenez has a job of",
        "answer": "cobbler"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adeline Reese has a job of",
        "answer": "juror"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Celia Leonard has a job of",
        "answer": "poet"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ricardo Lawson has a job of",
        "answer": "taxonomist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Phoebe Zuniga has a job of",
        "answer": "biographer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sincere Chan has a job of",
        "answer": "picnicker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hattie Rivas has a job of",
        "answer": "bidder"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aliza Frank has a job of",
        "answer": "photographer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Braylen Hicks has a job of",
        "answer": "mechanic"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alina Taylor has a job of",
        "answer": "military commander"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jackson McIntyre has a job of",
        "answer": "patient"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rebekah Blanchard has a job of",
        "answer": "smart lawyer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adler Vang has a job of",
        "answer": "student"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Madisyn Dougherty has a job of",
        "answer": "commander"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Asa Coffey has a job of",
        "answer": "preacher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paola Garner has a job of",
        "answer": "financier"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sage Hebert has a job of",
        "answer": "sage"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alonso Walter has a job of",
        "answer": "pioneer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Penny Peralta has a job of",
        "answer": "creditor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dangelo Archer has a job of",
        "answer": "bright person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kadence Fitzgerald has a job of",
        "answer": "hostess"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Peyton Buck has a job of",
        "answer": "disney fan"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Livia Walker has a job of",
        "answer": "flatterer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Luke Hunter has a job of",
        "answer": "strongman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Khloe Duke has a job of",
        "answer": "home owner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kalel Stein has a job of",
        "answer": "movie star"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Leilany Boyd has a job of",
        "answer": "wine maker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Wren McGee has a job of",
        "answer": "meditator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Conner Lopez has a job of",
        "answer": "teacher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Joziah Fields has a job of",
        "answer": "high school freshman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mathew Compton has a job of",
        "answer": "greedy person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elina Tapia has a job of",
        "answer": "decorator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Samir Nielsen has a job of",
        "answer": "stage magician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vienna Salazar has a job of",
        "answer": "square dancer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brody Liu has a job of",
        "answer": "painter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kate Delgado has a job of",
        "answer": "scientist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Colt Short has a job of",
        "answer": "popular speaker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Cheyenne Holt has a job of",
        "answer": "chef"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Niko Houston has a job of",
        "answer": "handyman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lylah House has a job of",
        "answer": "party guest"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Yehuda Benjamin has a job of",
        "answer": "chess player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jianna Sutton has a job of",
        "answer": "writer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Warren Garza has a job of",
        "answer": "jazz man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "River Watkins has a job of",
        "answer": "herbalist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nash Blevins has a job of",
        "answer": "bad cook"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aila Bates has a job of",
        "answer": "landlady"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ellis Leach has a job of",
        "answer": "stock broker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Martha Bush has a job of",
        "answer": "lazy person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gloria Tucker has a job of",
        "answer": "rider"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ivan Liu has a job of",
        "answer": "ballet dancer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Manuel Sims has a job of",
        "answer": "postman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lena O\u2019Donnell has a job of",
        "answer": "college professor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lian Ellison has a job of",
        "answer": "beautiful woman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Raina Cano has a job of",
        "answer": "good salesperson"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Terry Lamb has a job of",
        "answer": "famous actor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Malachi McClain has a job of",
        "answer": "theater manager"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Marleigh Spencer has a job of",
        "answer": "carnival worker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ace Rowe has a job of",
        "answer": "good baseball player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Matilda Khan has a job of",
        "answer": "scout leader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kendrick Valencia has a job of",
        "answer": "sailor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Maddison Morrison has a job of",
        "answer": "jockey"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emersyn Nunez has a job of",
        "answer": "national guard"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Caden Buckley has a job of",
        "answer": "blind person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Theodora Stevens has a job of",
        "answer": "student in high school"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zachary Heath has a job of",
        "answer": "stripper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Amani Grimes has a job of",
        "answer": "late riser"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harlan Valentine has a job of",
        "answer": "good student"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "August Alexander has a job of",
        "answer": "minister"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kingston Andrade has a job of",
        "answer": "hurt person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emmy Reynolds has a job of",
        "answer": "pharmacist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vincent Gibson has a job of",
        "answer": "blackjack player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Eden Montgomery has a job of",
        "answer": "novelist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Maximiliano Pitts has a job of",
        "answer": "grocer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nala Kennedy has a job of",
        "answer": "heavy duty equipment operator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kaisley Brady has a job of",
        "answer": "babysitter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Reed Pugh has a job of",
        "answer": "donor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Landry Giles has a job of",
        "answer": "passenger"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kole Tanner has a job of",
        "answer": "biologist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Baylor Wheeler has a job of",
        "answer": "lecturer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sydney Rosas has a job of",
        "answer": "door to door salesman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Remi Cunningham has a job of",
        "answer": "professor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Marley Norris has a job of",
        "answer": "talented marketer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Cairo Preston has a job of",
        "answer": "positive person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Indie Ray has a job of",
        "answer": "sculpter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hannah Austin has a job of",
        "answer": "college counselor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Omar Kelley has a job of",
        "answer": "devious person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rosalie Patton has a job of",
        "answer": "shepherd"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Moises Harvey has a job of",
        "answer": "letter writer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nicole Carey has a job of",
        "answer": "consierges"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emely Waller has a job of",
        "answer": "gym instructor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Marley Kane has a job of",
        "answer": "line cook"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ellianna Bush has a job of",
        "answer": "quarterback"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tyson Good has a job of",
        "answer": "seller"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nathalia Sullivan has a job of",
        "answer": "skydiver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Evan Morse has a job of",
        "answer": "poor person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kairi Hartman has a job of",
        "answer": "good captain"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Baker Edwards has a job of",
        "answer": "publisher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ivy Shepard has a job of",
        "answer": "library patron"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Damari Stafford has a job of",
        "answer": "forger"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bridget Sullivan has a job of",
        "answer": "homemaker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Evan Matthews has a job of",
        "answer": "cricketer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lila Golden has a job of",
        "answer": "tactful person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Amias Perry has a job of",
        "answer": "cartoonist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Clara Calderon has a job of",
        "answer": "flexible person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Oakley Meadows has a job of",
        "answer": "computer operator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Pearl Harrison has a job of",
        "answer": "lucky player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gavin Frost has a job of",
        "answer": "patron"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paula Frye has a job of",
        "answer": "good cook"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Franco Patton has a job of",
        "answer": "polic officer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorelei Sutton has a job of",
        "answer": "sign painter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Warren Villanueva has a job of",
        "answer": "hairstylist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Monroe Arroyo has a job of",
        "answer": "ranger"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alberto Keith has a job of",
        "answer": "meteorologist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elyse Fitzgerald has a job of",
        "answer": "sculptor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tori Morales has a job of",
        "answer": "nimble thinker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aaron Travis has a job of",
        "answer": "business man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mazikee Woods has a job of",
        "answer": "contractor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zion Olsen has a job of",
        "answer": "piano tuner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Oaklyn Blackburn has a job of",
        "answer": "groundskeeper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elsie Delgado has a job of",
        "answer": "warehouseman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Colt Knight has a job of",
        "answer": "bike rider"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gracie Potts has a job of",
        "answer": "computer scientist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alfred Robertson has a job of",
        "answer": "great tennis player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harmony Ramos has a job of",
        "answer": "hairdresser"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Chandler Sloan has a job of",
        "answer": "signwriter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ocean Davidson has a job of",
        "answer": "prophet"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jayla Allison has a job of",
        "answer": "comedy club owner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aleena Hernandez has a job of",
        "answer": "reasonable person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mason Underwood has a job of",
        "answer": "generous loan officer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ensley Booker has a job of",
        "answer": "racer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dominik Lugo has a job of",
        "answer": "kind man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kaylie Ellison has a job of",
        "answer": "bungee jumper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kye Arellano has a job of",
        "answer": "dockworker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Faye Hanna has a job of",
        "answer": "reporter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aydin Haley has a job of",
        "answer": "rescuer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Addilynn Wyatt has a job of",
        "answer": "meter man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Sam Lambert has a job of",
        "answer": "fertile husband"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nina Pugh has a job of",
        "answer": "grocery clerk"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Judson Andrews has a job of",
        "answer": "press secretary"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Payton Benson has a job of",
        "answer": "journalist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Desmond McCormick has a job of",
        "answer": "sergeant"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Macie Galvan has a job of",
        "answer": "video game player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kingsley Beasley has a job of",
        "answer": "hunter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jaylah Estes has a job of",
        "answer": "physician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hakeem Andersen has a job of",
        "answer": "trainer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zoie Howard has a job of",
        "answer": "conductor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bianca Blanchard has a job of",
        "answer": "psychologist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adler Higgins has a job of",
        "answer": "dishonest clerk"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Leighton Cuevas has a job of",
        "answer": "department head"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brecken Shaw has a job of",
        "answer": "sick person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jorge Briggs has a job of",
        "answer": "home gardener"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Alia Avalos has a job of",
        "answer": "pianst"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ariya Enriquez has a job of",
        "answer": "woodsman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rebecca Henson has a job of",
        "answer": "dishonest person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bellamy Yang has a job of",
        "answer": "record producer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Angelina Fitzpatrick has a job of",
        "answer": "real estate agent"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Blaze Conley has a job of",
        "answer": "telemarketer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Salem McLean has a job of",
        "answer": "hotel clerk"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Crosby Pennington has a job of",
        "answer": "private detective"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jorge Wade has a job of",
        "answer": "good swimmer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Evie McMahon has a job of",
        "answer": "cashier"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jakob Hampton has a job of",
        "answer": "petitioner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Leona Gray has a job of",
        "answer": "science teacher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nicholas Silva has a job of",
        "answer": "dancer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lucia Espinoza has a job of",
        "answer": "clueless person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Damien Aguirre has a job of",
        "answer": "law enforcement officer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ariah Dominguez has a job of",
        "answer": "seaman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kaden Moon has a job of",
        "answer": "serious student"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Frankie Simpson has a job of",
        "answer": "dairy maid"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Anastasia Rivers has a job of",
        "answer": "trustworthy person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bear Bailey has a job of",
        "answer": "stenographer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ezra Hoffman has a job of",
        "answer": "card dealer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aspen McMillan has a job of",
        "answer": "governor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rocky Houston has a job of",
        "answer": "shoemaker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lylah Lindsey has a job of",
        "answer": "musican"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jayson Newton has a job of",
        "answer": "millionaire"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Charles Newton has a job of",
        "answer": "yoga master"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Braelynn Shannon has a job of",
        "answer": "bike mechanic"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Eliel Richmond has a job of",
        "answer": "climber"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Whitney Medrano has a job of",
        "answer": "zookeeper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Arian Rojas has a job of",
        "answer": "veteran"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Adaline Ford has a job of",
        "answer": "rock star"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Luis McKenzie has a job of",
        "answer": "jeweler"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Briar Beard has a job of",
        "answer": "mailman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nathanael Nelson has a job of",
        "answer": "postalworker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Everly Banks has a job of",
        "answer": "military analyst"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Juliana Mullins has a job of",
        "answer": "great athlete"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Allen White has a job of",
        "answer": "sentry"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Layla Webb has a job of",
        "answer": "dog trainer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lorenzo Williamson has a job of",
        "answer": "job hunter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Catherine Schultz has a job of",
        "answer": "comedian"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Enoch Wade has a job of",
        "answer": "wagonmaster"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Evie Fox has a job of",
        "answer": "maintenance man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Antonio Lawrence has a job of",
        "answer": "prayerful person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lauren Mahoney has a job of",
        "answer": "spammer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Azariah Harvey has a job of",
        "answer": "contestant"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nicole Levy has a job of",
        "answer": "taskmaster"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harold Whitaker has a job of",
        "answer": "body builder"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ivanna Carson has a job of",
        "answer": "hiker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ares Cherry has a job of",
        "answer": "host"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Boden Barber has a job of",
        "answer": "shopowner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Cassidy Proctor has a job of",
        "answer": "busdriver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vance Chen has a job of",
        "answer": "janitor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Valeria Jennings has a job of",
        "answer": "football player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Corbin Klein has a job of",
        "answer": "beautician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "David Clarke has a job of",
        "answer": "policaman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elisha Berg has a job of",
        "answer": "senator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emmalyn Everett has a job of",
        "answer": "metalworker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Camilo Winters has a job of",
        "answer": "highway patrolman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kataleya Velasquez has a job of",
        "answer": "race car driver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elyse Branch has a job of",
        "answer": "housewife"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Keenan Bowers has a job of",
        "answer": "puzzle fan"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elisa Middleton has a job of",
        "answer": "professional witness"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Misael Knox has a job of",
        "answer": "good chef"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kallie Phelps has a job of",
        "answer": "scrabble player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hamza Dominguez has a job of",
        "answer": "careless smoker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Raegan Conrad has a job of",
        "answer": "rich person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dilan Barnes has a job of",
        "answer": "leader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Liliana Cortes has a job of",
        "answer": "telephone operator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paulina Patrick has a job of",
        "answer": "vendor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Derrick Hill has a job of",
        "answer": "skilled lathe operator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hannah Novak has a job of",
        "answer": "lifeguard"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bishop Foster has a job of",
        "answer": "beutiful young lady"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brielle Franco has a job of",
        "answer": "traffic cop"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Gage Singh has a job of",
        "answer": "stunt man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vivienne Monroe has a job of",
        "answer": "sniper"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Colby Gray has a job of",
        "answer": "police officer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kara Stanley has a job of",
        "answer": "good speaker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Manuel Solis has a job of",
        "answer": "competitor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Miracle Leal has a job of",
        "answer": "socialite"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Cedric Monroe has a job of",
        "answer": "competitive person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Carly Tang has a job of",
        "answer": "stubborn person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rogelio Roman has a job of",
        "answer": "technical support worker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Cason Alvarez has a job of",
        "answer": "bell ringer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Leilani Carroll has a job of",
        "answer": "road crew"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Oscar Swanson has a job of",
        "answer": "miser"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ocean Bates has a job of",
        "answer": "physicist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Eduardo Zimmerman has a job of",
        "answer": "bishop"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ariyah Bell has a job of",
        "answer": "bricklayer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emmett Hebert has a job of",
        "answer": "waitress"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kyleigh Neal has a job of",
        "answer": "magician"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hadley Lucero has a job of",
        "answer": "catcher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paige Faulkner has a job of",
        "answer": "bicyclist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jabari Hardin has a job of",
        "answer": "celebrity"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vada Walker has a job of",
        "answer": "talented cook"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Luke McCullough has a job of",
        "answer": "creator"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hana Decker has a job of",
        "answer": "coach"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jane Schmitt has a job of",
        "answer": "kindergarten teacher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Murphy Gutierrez has a job of",
        "answer": "distributor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Savannah Maxwell has a job of",
        "answer": "migrant worker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Eden Mills has a job of",
        "answer": "prankster"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Laurel Villa has a job of",
        "answer": "renter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Clay Cano has a job of",
        "answer": "friendly person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Egypt Knight has a job of",
        "answer": "paddler"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Beckett Shepard has a job of",
        "answer": "venture capitalist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Noor Nolan has a job of",
        "answer": "receptionist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Maximo Rosas has a job of",
        "answer": "gorgeous guy"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Joelle Mitchell has a job of",
        "answer": "trumpeter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jaxon Jaramillo has a job of",
        "answer": "modest person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bentlee Ortega has a job of",
        "answer": "milkman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lilah Woodard has a job of",
        "answer": "bad driver"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Westley Ahmed has a job of",
        "answer": "graduate student"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jolie Graves has a job of",
        "answer": "locksmith"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Cesar Leal has a job of",
        "answer": "good bowler"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Eli Jarvis has a job of",
        "answer": "hacker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Elisabeth Wilkinson has a job of",
        "answer": "bartender"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Leonard Koch has a job of",
        "answer": "therapist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Milana Garrett has a job of",
        "answer": "basebaseball batter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kairo Rose has a job of",
        "answer": "smart farmer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Magnolia Murray has a job of",
        "answer": "trucker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Hanna Walls has a job of",
        "answer": "shoeshiner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Maria Choi has a job of",
        "answer": "delivery person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Khari Conrad has a job of",
        "answer": "skateboarder"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Atlas Lowe has a job of",
        "answer": "good athlete"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Amari McIntosh has a job of",
        "answer": "thrifty person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kristian Underwood has a job of",
        "answer": "basketball player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Ensley Maxwell has a job of",
        "answer": "madame chairman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Eden Atkinson has a job of",
        "answer": "skilled actor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jazmin Gross has a job of",
        "answer": "midwife"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Quinn Ryan has a job of",
        "answer": "fiction writer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Morgan Marshall has a job of",
        "answer": "banker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kaiden McIntosh has a job of",
        "answer": "cowboy"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Chaim Blackwell has a job of",
        "answer": "fireman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Saoirse Miranda has a job of",
        "answer": "wise parent"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rory Salas has a job of",
        "answer": "dieter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Fletcher Beltran has a job of",
        "answer": "chessplayer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kaydence Ware has a job of",
        "answer": "late worker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brynleigh Carlson has a job of",
        "answer": "greedy merchant"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Paul Ibarra has a job of",
        "answer": "linguist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Madilynn Lam has a job of",
        "answer": "good writer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Bodie Ho has a job of",
        "answer": "clerk without customer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Calliope Lawrence has a job of",
        "answer": "bank teller"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kaleb Bender has a job of",
        "answer": "president of company"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lilyana Duarte has a job of",
        "answer": "marathon runner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Abdullah Mercado has a job of",
        "answer": "barman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Mckinley Wall has a job of",
        "answer": "programmer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Issac Christensen has a job of",
        "answer": "president"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Carmen Leach has a job of",
        "answer": "bass player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Melany Walker has a job of",
        "answer": "revolutionary"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Luke Guerra has a job of",
        "answer": "young person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Edith Hunt has a job of",
        "answer": "helpful person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Jesus Liu has a job of",
        "answer": "harbor pilot"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kate Conrad has a job of",
        "answer": "sensitive person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Dilan Richardson has a job of",
        "answer": "mechanical engineer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Banks Roach has a job of",
        "answer": "bouncer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lyanna Gonzales has a job of",
        "answer": "strong man"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brayden Hampton has a job of",
        "answer": "scholar"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Leona Goodman has a job of",
        "answer": "card player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emmalyn Reyna has a job of",
        "answer": "sommelier"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Reginald Boyd has a job of",
        "answer": "fish farmer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Georgia Gross has a job of",
        "answer": "strong leader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Quinn Mullins has a job of",
        "answer": "rationalist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Maliyah Munoz has a job of",
        "answer": "dressmaker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Justin Rangel has a job of",
        "answer": "wise person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Eliel Serrano has a job of",
        "answer": "deep sea fisherman"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Allie Cordova has a job of",
        "answer": "lawyer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Maison Dalton has a job of",
        "answer": "music lover"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lilian Cherry has a job of",
        "answer": "good dealer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Rome Kennedy has a job of",
        "answer": "chemist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brianna Eaton has a job of",
        "answer": "botonist"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Anaya Cross has a job of",
        "answer": "hitter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Fabian Donovan has a job of",
        "answer": "recluse"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Azariah Wang has a job of",
        "answer": "boxer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Cohen Serrano has a job of",
        "answer": "notary"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Allie Glass has a job of",
        "answer": "good cabinet maker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Allan Pitts has a job of",
        "answer": "broker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Nala McIntosh has a job of",
        "answer": "dwarf"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kristian Lamb has a job of",
        "answer": "solicitor"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Kyree Gibbs has a job of",
        "answer": "great baker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Carter Contreras has a job of",
        "answer": "sorrowful person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Princess Frazier has a job of",
        "answer": "surgeon"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Callum Espinosa has a job of",
        "answer": "diplomat"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Xavier Gomez has a job of",
        "answer": "marketer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Julian Martinez has a job of",
        "answer": "good soccer player"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Harper Lawson has a job of",
        "answer": "drycleaner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Emani Gillespie has a job of",
        "answer": "curious person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Forest Hoffman has a job of",
        "answer": "showgirl"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Aspen Davis has a job of",
        "answer": "high school graduate"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lucas Stokes has a job of",
        "answer": "protester"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Miranda Larson has a job of",
        "answer": "client"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Brinley Gilbert has a job of",
        "answer": "plumber"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tobias Vo has a job of",
        "answer": "responsible adult"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Artemis Fitzpatrick has a job of",
        "answer": "skinny person"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Roselyn Clark has a job of",
        "answer": "sorter"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "John Hahn has a job of",
        "answer": "good worker"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Fallon Hester has a job of",
        "answer": "blacksmith"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Vanessa Nash has a job of",
        "answer": "sharp trader"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Chandler Jaramillo has a job of",
        "answer": "farmer"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Guadalupe Kelley has a job of",
        "answer": "substitute teacher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Connor Stevens has a job of",
        "answer": "salesperson"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Katherine Potter has a job of",
        "answer": "great cook"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Cheyenne Little has a job of",
        "answer": "wrestler"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Lennox Harding has a job of",
        "answer": "school principal"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Zaiden Thompson has a job of",
        "answer": "gunner"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Finn Ball has a job of",
        "answer": "cattle rancher"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Axton Crosby has a job of",
        "answer": "busboy"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Keily Moran has a job of",
        "answer": "doctoral candidate"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Tate Kaur has a job of",
        "answer": "principal"
    },
    {
        "prompt": "Miles Norris has a job of",
        "answer": "ballerina"
    }
]